[
    {
      "question": "How many cats do I have?",
      "options": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
      "answer": ["2"]
    },
    {
      "question": "When were my two cats born?",
      "options": ["11/6/2024", "10/14/2024", "09/27/2024", "08/15/2024", "07/11/2024"],
      "answer": ["10/14/2024", "09/27/2024"],
      "isMultipleChoice": true
    },
    {
      "question": "What are my cats' names?",
      "options": ["Noodle", "Mochi", "Molly", "Theo"],
      "answer": ["Molly", "Theo"],
      "isMultipleChoice": true
    },
    {
      "question": "Is Molly a female?",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Is Theo a male?",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is my cats' favorite canned food?",
      "options": ["Tiki Cat", "Wellness Core", "Orijen"],
      "answer": ["Tiki Cat"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Are my cats outdoor cats?",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": ["False"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What color is Molly?",
      "options": ["Black and white", "Orange", "Ragdoll"],
      "answer": ["Black and white"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Molly’s best friend?",
      "options": ["Theo", "Mumu", "Kiki"],
      "answer": ["Mumu"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What color are my cats’ collars?",
      "options": ["Baby pink", "Baby blue", "Sage green", "Purple", "Black"],
      "answer": ["Baby pink", "Sage green"],
      "isMultipleChoice": true
    }
  ]
  